beat the egg and butter.
animation
If there is a hole, bake the egg Yolk.
bake the egg Yolk in a preheated oven at 180°C for 30 minutes.
Hiya-senpai, I'm sorry for helping you with that.
Thank you for the shower.
I went back home because it was a hot day.
Oh, that's right.
You still have the bill you bought yesterday, right?
Can I drink it?
It's a luxury to have a bill from the morning of the weekday.
Hiya-senpai, are you angry after all?
You're angry, aren't you?
Do I look like I'm angry?
I'm not going to refuse the request from the cute junior, am I right?
But I asked you to do that.
You asked a lot of people to do it, so you contacted me, right?
No, I'm not.
I'm a senior.
If you're a senior, I'm sure you'll do it.
I'm the only one who has a car.
Well, I was happy that you were counting on me.
Really?
But you promised to keep my request.
Of course.
What about your request?
Anyway, don't you drink beer now?
You haven't been drinking since yesterday, right?
No, I haven't.
I'm tired.
Hey, Yuria-senpai.
Do you have to go to work today?
No.
I got a job early this morning, so I'm fine.
Yuria-senpai.
Do you really think Kousuki-kun isn't angry with you?
Since I was in 9th grade, Kousuki-kun was a student, right?
That's why you two got married, right?
Yes, but...
But recently, Kousuki-kun seems to have met another woman and me.
Hey, did you get drunk with the beer you drank earlier?
No, I didn't.
But I've been worried about it for a long time and couldn't sleep.
That's why you called me out in the middle of the night to solve that problem, right?
And you solved it with me.
That's why I'm going to end this story.
I'm going to sleep today, and I'm going to tell you all the bad things.
Hey, senpai.
But...
There's no reason.
Hey, what do you think?
Will you listen to my request from now on?
What do you mean?
That's what I mean.
I was surprised.
I've always liked Towa since I was a student.
But I've never done anything like that.
You're going to listen to my request, right?
Then, leave it to me.
Right?
Right.
Don't look at me like that.
Right?
You don't like me, do you?
Hey, open your mouth.
I'm going to think about your wish.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I don't know how to kiss you.
Wait.
Let me do it.
What's wrong?
Why do you keep doing this?
Miria-senpai.
Kissing a girl like this makes me feel so good.
I...
I think I can forget about you, Kosuke.
I doubted my parents.
Why don't you kiss a girl like this?
It has nothing to do with it.
Kosuke made me feel uneasy.
That's why I can do it.
I finally got it.
Well, from now on, we are lovers.
That's good.
That's why you can call me by my name.
Got it?
I'll do it.
Kiss.
Come here.
I can see you.
What are you laughing at?
Do you want to kiss me?
Wait a minute.
Are you a little stronger?
Do you want to see me?
Why are you laughing at me?
I'm sorry.
I can see you.
Show me.
Are you embarrassed?
Wait a minute.
Do you like it?
It's nice.
It's nice?
It's cute.
I'm back.
Do you want to kiss me?
Are you embarrassed?
It's nice.
It's hard.
Do you like it?
Are you embarrassed?
It's moving.
I'm back.
Let me hear it.
Are you embarrassed?
Here.
I'm changing my mind.
I'm going to let you go.
I'm going to let you go because I'm small.
I'm coming out.
I'm going to let you go.
What's wrong?
I'm getting embarrassed.
Do you understand that I'm getting embarrassed too?
I'm going to let you go.
What's wrong with you?
You're getting embarrassed.
I'm going to let you go.
What's wrong?
Do you want to bite me?
I'm going to let you go.
What's wrong?
Here you go.
Don't run away.
I'm going to let you go.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Here you go.
I'm going to let you go.
I'm used to it.
Here you go.
If you get so drunk, you'll get in.
I'm going to let you go.
Here you go.
I'm going to...
You're done.
You're embarrassing.
You're happy, right?
No?
Show me.
Oh, wow.
You're embarrassing.
You're embarrassing?
Don't run away.
You're embarrassing.
How was it?
Did you feel good?
Good night.
Hey.
What's in this room?
What is it?
It's Kousuke's room, isn't it?
Didn't you sleep with Kousuke?
Yeah.
I don't want to sleep with him.
Then...
Why did you sleep in that room?
Because we...
We were in love.
Hey.
We're in love, aren't we?
You're still worried about Kousuke, aren't you?
That's not true.
You're trying to change me and Kousuke, aren't you?
You're not going to do that, are you?
Don't be shy.
Forget it.
It's okay now, isn't it?
Let's stop here.
Why?
Why are you trying to do this?
It's Kousuke's change, isn't it?
It's not like that.
But just look at me.
Why can't you understand?
But we're dating, aren't we?
That's right.
Then...
I'll do it here.
It's not like that.
You're cute, aren't you?
Are you always like this?
I'm scared.
Kousuke.
Do you want me to touch you?
Touch me?
Who do you want?
Kousuke.
Your back is moving.
Here?
This hard part?
Hey.
Don't move that much.
I'm closing my eyes.
Don't you want it to get dirty?
Kousuke.
What are you doing?
So don't move that much.
Hey.
Here.
You feel good, don't you?
Then...
Please feel better with me.
Kousuke.
Your back is moving.
It hurts.
I feel good.
Kousuke.
Your legs.
Your hands are wide.
Kousuke.
It hurts.
Are you done?
I feel so good.
Kousuke.
Sorry.
My neck hurts.
Wait.
Kousuke.
It hurts a lot.
Are you okay?
Kousuke.
It hurts a lot.
I've always wanted to drink Yuriyama.
Why?
It hurts.
Show me.
It hurts a lot.
I can't do anything.
It hurts.
It hurts a lot.
Wait.
You were happy.
I don't remember anymore.
But that's because of you, Ilya.
You made me feel bad.
It's not like that.
I was in love with you as a husband.
I was in love with you.
I was in love with KOSUKI.
When you look at my face,
you get excited right away.
And you get excited.
It's like a dog.
I...
That's...
Hey.
There's something I want to do today.
It's good, isn't it?
KOSUKI
Hey.
I don't want to be like this.
I just want to play with you as a woman.
It's okay.
Look at this.
KOSUKI
Ilya, you feel good, don't you?
You look like a boy.
I don't want to.
KOSUKI
Wait.
I don't want to.
KOSUKI
I want to.
I don't want to.
I'm going to use this.
I want to.
I don't want to.
Can I beautiful it in the mirror?
Can I?
I'm disappointed.
I want to do it again.
Kiss me properly.
A little more.
I don't want to.
Let's do it together.
Come here and push me.
I don't want to.
I feel good.
I'll give you a reward today.
This is my area.
I knew it.
Who was it?
It's not me.
I was told by Kousuke.
You don't have to do that.
Now I have you.
You can't break it easily.
If it breaks,
I'll throw it away.
Like Kousuke.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.