NO!
I'm a new fan of the new kind of girl.
I'm Hamasaki Mao.
In the past, I used to be an IT writer who introduced the latest digital content in the computer magazine.
But one day, I came out with something that I was a lesbian.
After that, I was sent to an essay that said that I had my own sexual experience.
I left after Lily's injury.
That became the best seller.
Now that I'm a popular writer, I'm listening to various media articles such as the Socialist Essay written by Lesbian.
When I was a student, I was shocked to see Lily's injury after Mr. Hamasaki's injury.
Because of that, I hoped for a job at the publishing company.
I worked hard to get a job.
I did everything to work with Mr. Hamasaki Mao.
Wait a minute, Shinjin-chan.
You've been looking at me too much lately.
You can't concentrate on your job, can you?
I wanted to see Mr. Hamasaki Mao's job in front of me.
It's okay if you take permission from the editor.
I'm glad you said that, but I always work alone, so it's hard to do it while I'm watching.
I was so moved by reading Lily's injury in my school days.
I wanted to see Mr. Hamasaki Mao someday.
That dream came true today.
Hey, Shinjin-chan.
I'm Minami Momoko.
My name is Minami.
My name is Hiragana.
If you call me by my name, please call me Momoko-chan.
Momoko-chan?
I'll send you an e-mail if it's done.
So you don't have to wait here.
But it's better to take it from the company and check it.
It's better if I check the time and date here.
Isn't it efficient?
Time and date?
I shouldn't have made such a mistake.
It's okay. I'll write it down soon.
Take a good look at it.
Momoko-chan?
Yes, I'll do it.
After coming out of being a lesbian, my life changed.
In the past, I couldn't accept the fact that I was a homosexual.
But when I was able to fall in love with a homosexual for the first time,
I finally accepted myself as a lesbian.
I was able to accept myself as a lesbian for the first time.
After that, I began to express what I was a lesbian,
and I began to follow the happy days with my lover as an essay.
That essay gathered the attention of the world,
and finally became a best-seller,
which has been passed down and passed away.
However, my success was in vain,
and my lover left me.
The reason for that was that I couldn't meet the person I was a homosexual.
I was too much of a sad person,
and I became self-conscious.
I had a female relationship that didn't exist,
and I began to write an essay that was more intense.
Even on a daily basis, it became a topic,
and I became able to see myself as a writer,
representing a homosexual.
Good morning.
Teacher, I'm sorry for bothering you.
No, no.
I just wanted to change my mood.
And today's Momo-chan is like a customer to me.
Teacher, thank you very much.
Instead of that, would you like to talk to me a little?
That would be nice, right?
Of course.
I'm happy.
Oh.
I'll eat this.
This tea is very delicious.
Teacher, where did you buy this?
It's called Lonefeld.
It's a high-class tea from Germany.
Lonefeld?
It's a high-class tea that Lili's lover's father liked.
You're my fan, aren't you?
Yes, it's a high-class tea that my lover used to like.
I don't have any complaints about it,
but I can't give up on it for some reason.
Is that so?
I cried over and over again in that farewell scene.
The two of us, who were together,
drank the same cup of tea and kissed at the end.
At that time, we kissed crying together,
so the tea was a little salty.
But I understand that feeling very well.
Because I'm also a lesbian.
What?
Can you tell me a little more about that?
That's why I know Lili and Shushu very well.
No, no.
I don't care about my work.
Mo-chan is a lesbian?
Yes, but what's that?
Tell me a little more.
There was a guy who was a student,
but he was really bad at entering the circle with his boyfriend.
He was attacked by his boyfriend and his friends.
I thought it was hard.
I'm sorry.
A guy is really bad at entering the circle.
But it's okay.
I'm a lesbian.
I'll heal your broken heart.
Turn around.
No, I don't need that.
Mo-chan, you came to see me, didn't you?
You're both a lesbian, aren't you?
There's no problem.
I also want to date a teacher I admire,
but is it necessary to date a lesbian?
The pattern I know is completely different.
What's your favorite way to date a girl?
I think it's a heart-to-heart relationship,
so I drink alcohol and drinks in the morning.
No, that's a unique way of dating.
I don't know.
I can't help it.
I'll teach you the real way to date a girl.
It's okay, Momo.
I can't help it.
I knew it.
It's so cute.
It's soft.
It's a pillow.
It's cute.
How was it?
It's a pillow.
I don't think I hated it.
My body is getting hot.
I can't run away.
Do you think it's a pillow?
Let me hear it.
My body is getting hot.
I was hiding such a big thing.
I was hiding it.
It's a pillow.
I like it here.
I'm tired.
Can you show me?
It's hot.
It's a pillow.
I like it.
I want you to touch it.
It's cute.
It's a pillow.
Where is it?
I can't find it.
I can see it well.
It's a pillow.
I can't see it.
What's wrong?
It's a pillow.
What is it called?
Tell me.
It's a pillow.
Do you like a pillow?
Really?
I don't like it.
I like it.
It's a pillow.
I'm going to hide my body.
I'm going to tell you how to sleep.
It's a pillow.
What's wrong?
I'm going to sleep.
It's a pillow.
I'm sweating.
I don't like it.
I'm glad you like it.
It's a pillow.
I don't like it.
I want you to sleep.
It's a pillow.
I'm going to make you feel good.
Do you want me to eat it?
Why are you so shiny?
Why?
I want you to lick it.
Do you want me to lick it?
I can't lick it.
I want you to lick it.
I can hear you.
Please lick it.
I can't lick it.
I can smell something.
I want you to lick it.
I can't lick it.
It's good.
Let me lick it.
I can't move my legs.
I can't lick it.
Did you feel good?
I was scolded a lot.
I feel a little bad.
Don't say such a lonely thing.
I can't lick it.
It's good.
Why are you sweating?
Wait a minute.
I can't lick it.
Where should I go?
It's here.
I think I've been doing this for a long time.
It's kind of tight.
Did you lick it?
That's right.
Actually, I feel better after being bitten.
I can't lick it.
What's that smell?
Bye.
I can't lick it.
Look at me.
I wonder what's going on.
Is it embarrassing?
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I can't lick it.
It's cute.
It's pretty.
Open it up.
I want to see it better.
Hurry up.
It's coming out.
What do you feel now?
I feel like I've been bitten.
What do you feel?
What?
I feel like I've been bitten.
I'm so excited.
I want to see it better.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to lick it?
You don't like it, do you?
Do you want me to teach you?
What do you want me to do?
I feel like I've been bitten.
I can't lick it.
Do you want me to lick it?
I feel like I've been bitten.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to lick it?
I feel like I've been bitten.
Do you want me to stop it?
I don't know what to say.
Do you want me to leave it to you?
I feel like I've been bitten.
No, no, no, no, no.
Do you want me to lick it?
I feel like I've been bitten.
Do you want me to leave it to you?
No, no, no, no, no.
I want to leave it to you.
Do you want me to lick it?
Do you want me to leave it to you?
I'll let you lick it.
I feel like I've been bitten.
Are you feeling better?
You're so mean.
I feel like you're going to cry alone.
I don't feel so good yet.
Come on.
Hey, let me go.
I knew it.
Do you want to quit?
I feel so bad.
Please take care of me.
Let me show you.
You should look closer.
Come here.
Tell me how I feel.
I feel so bad.
What is this place?
This place.
I like this place.
Please don't.
I feel so bad.
What is this place?
You look at me.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Oh no, oh no.
I feel so bad.
I can't stop.
Oh no, oh no.
I feel so bad.
Don't do that.
I feel so so bad.
I feel so bad.
What do you think?
This is the real resume.
It looks so bad.
Really?
This is it?
Mr. Masaki.
I understand.
I don't have a lot of female resume experience.
It's not like that.
What?
The real reason why I became a resume is
because I fell in love with a man.
During my school days,
I had a lot of men in the circle.
But there was no one who was satisfied with me.
At that time,
Julia was the one who got me into a resume in the city.
When I was interested in it,
I tried to get into it with her.
But she got me into it 53 times in just 2 hours.
After that,
I got into the resume play.
I couldn't meet a woman who had more technical skills than Julia.
At that time,
I lost interest in the resume play.
Tomorrow night,
I will tell you the truth about me.
I'll be waiting for you here tomorrow.
On the way to Bottom up
Sara and Julia
Wait for me for a moment, please.
I'll teach you the real sex.
All of a sudden...
I can't take it anymore.
Ouch!
Scary.
I'll die.
Ouch!
I'm so scared.
No, don't!
No, don't eat it!
Ouch!
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so scared.
Ouch!
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
Hey, Mao-san.
From this time on,
you should make our relationship a secret.
I don't want you to say it,
but you're right.
From this time on,
you should make our relationship a secret.
Then,
let's make our relationship a secret.
I'm so scared.
Mao-san, please take a good look.
What's the point of this?
You can love me, right?
I'm so scared.
Have you ever seen something like this?
Do you want to lick it?
I'm so scared.
Why are you so scared??
You become scared word by word.
Can you do something like this?
He won't understand.
Ah!!
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Don't cough.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I like you.
You're so cute.
I'm sorry.
I wanna die.
I wanna go!
You don't recognize me, right?
Give me your face!
I'm sorry.
I wanna go!
Give me your face!
Mom, thanks to you, I can draw better than I imagined.
That's great.
I'm happy that you can draw better than I imagined.
I don't care about that.
I want a perfect ending.
What?
Please leave it to me.
I haven't experienced it yet.
I have something to take.
But you have something to take.
Give me your face!
Did you fall asleep?
Yes, I did.
Wake up.
What should I do?
I love you.
Wake up.
You've never helped me, right?
Good morning.
It's been a month since I last saw you.
You seem to be popular.
Of course.
I'm the only one who can put on such a lively face.
If you keep going like this,
I told the editor that there is a dating culture.
Really?
What?
Are you happy?
Really?
I'm happy.
Wake up.
I have to be more active.
Well,
there are a few days left until the deadline,
so I have to work harder.
Of course.
My teacher's secret meeting.
Wait a minute.
I thought it was a meeting.
I didn't know the details.
Teacher, do you hate meeting?
No.
I don't like it.
Then, today,
I'm going to buy a teacher's secret meeting.
I'm going to play with it for a while.
What?
Is that it?
Please subscribe to my channel.