I'm just a little bit tired.
I thought my life was the worst.
I was bullied by high school in the mid-term.
I failed in my exams.
I didn't even get to know the F-Land University that I made it to.
I spent every day of my life.
Are you cold?
No, I'm hot.
I've always thought this day would last forever.
But I met her and everything changed.
Here's the orange.
Wait a minute.
The room is dirty.
Haruto.
Are you a friend?
No, I'm not.
Are you?
You're my girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
I live next to you.
I'm Runa Tsukino.
I'm Haruto and I'm a childhood friend.
Nice to meet you. I'm Yuzu Shura.
Nice to meet you.
You're cute.
What did you do?
Tell me.
You're going to the F-Land University.
Where did you go?
I went to work.
You don't have to work.
I don't want to draw your eyes.
I just want you to look good.
You have a good personality.
No, I don't want to.
Haruto didn't have a girlfriend for a long time.
So I was worried.
But I'm glad I met a good person.
Haruto.
Hey, Haruto.
Are you in the way?
Excuse me.
You're a good person.
Haruto.
I couldn't study and I couldn't be friends with my friends.
Really?
But Runa-chan was my best friend.
Did you like him?
No, I didn't like him.
I like him.
He's my only friend.
Really?
Yes.
I like Yuzu-chan.
If Yuzu-chan is here, that's all I need.
I'm so happy today.
But...
Haruto.
Do you like him?
Yes, I do.
Let's hurry up.
Wow, you're so big.
I'll put it in.
Take it easy.
Yes.
I like him.
Yuzu-chan.
What's wrong?
I like him.
Yuzu-san.
Hi.
You look good.
I'm Yuzu-san.
Hi.
You look good.
Do you have a date with Haruto?
I don't have a date with Haruto.
I see. Do you have time?
Yes, I do.
Can I talk to you?
Yes.
I want to get closer to Yuzu-san.
That's good.
Yes.
It was cold.
It's gone.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Is this sake?
Yes, hot wine.
It warms up the body.
It gets better.
It's good.
Really?
Yes.
It's good.
It has a beautiful effect.
But Yuzu-san doesn't need it.
Your skin is beautiful.
No, no.
It's slippery.
Do you like grilled meat?
I like it.
You like meat?
Yes, I like it.
I like hormone.
It's good.
I want to get closer to Yuzu-san.
Can I call you Yuzu?
Yes, it's good.
Really?
Can you call me Luna?
Yes, I can.
Yuzu?
Luna?
Yes.
You can call me Yuzu.
Yes, I can.
Yuzu?
Yes, you can call me Yuzu.
Yes, I can.
But I'm happy.
Call me Yuzu.
Hey,
Do you like Haruto?
What?
Where?
A kind place?
Yes.
For example,
I have a bad job that everyone doesn't do at work.
But he does it for me.
What about Haruto?
Yes.
I'm often scolded by the manager.
But when I see him like that,
he's cute.
He doesn't let me go.
I want to be by his side.
It's like that.
I see.
Did you like Haruto?
It's not like that.
I'm not interested in men.
What?
I like Haruto more than men.
Here?
Yes.
Yuzu,
have you ever done this?
What?
No, I haven't.
So,
have you ever done this?
No, I haven't.
No?
I mean,
I have Haruto.
I see.
I was surprised all of a sudden.
Are you okay?
Can you help me?
No.
Okay.
Then,
can I have some milk?
Sure.
Your hair is so fluffy.
You have long eyelashes.
You're so cute.
Your lips are so soft.
Your eyes are so soft.
You're so cute.
What's wrong?
Yuzu and I want to get closer.
Are you nervous?
Aren't you getting hot?
I'm okay.
What's wrong?
I drank alcohol.
Are you okay?
No, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
I'm not okay.
Look at me.
Your eyes are so beautiful.
I'm okay.
I thought you were cute all the time.
Don't look at me.
You're cute.
Can I kiss you?
No.
You can't?
I'm going crazy.
Are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
I'm not crazy.
I'm like a friend's manager.
Your eyes are so beautiful.
I'm okay.
Show me your tongue.
Your mouth.
Your tongue is beautiful.
Show me your tongue.
Your tongue is so soft.
Do you feel good?
Don't pull me.
Show me your tongue.
Which one is longer?
I'm going crazy.
Show me your tongue.
Your eyes are so beautiful.
You're cute.
You're so cute.
Show me your tongue.
Are you okay?
Are you scared?
Yes.
It's okay to make a big sound like when you're doing it.
I heard it.
It's so cute because it's so thin here.
It was a round sound.
Show me your tongue.
Don't stop.
I'm going to do it too.
It's not embarrassing.
Show me your tongue.
Your tongue is so cute.
Did you think you were going to be removed?
Did you want me to be removed?
Did you want me to touch here more?
Take it yourself.
Show me.
Are you okay?
It's so pretty.
It's soft.
The color of your neck is so pretty.
It's so small.
Show me your tongue.
Did you want to kiss me now?
It's so cute.
Show me your tongue.
It stinks.
Have you ever been teased by Haruto?
No.
Show me your tongue.
It's soft.
Your butt is so pretty.
Show me your tongue.
It's so pretty.
It's so cute.
Show me your tongue.
It's so pretty.
It's getting hot.
Show me your tongue.
So cute.
It's so cute.
Stop it.
You have a good one.
Can I use it?
Do you know what this is?
It's my chinchin.
Do you want to put it in?
I want to put it in.
I'll do it gently, so it's okay.
It hurts, doesn't it?
It hurts.
I'll do it slowly.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
It's so cute.
Hello?
Can't you see me from now on?
Today,
I can't.
I have a friend.
I see.
I'll call you again.
See you.
Okay.
Izu-chan,
I haven't seen you lately.
Haruto?
What did you say?
I said I won't see you today.
Hmm.
To be honest,
I want to be separated from Haruto.
But you look so pitiful.
What about me?
Yuzu,
don't you like me?
Hmm.
That's right.
I like you too.
You like me too?
You don't like me?
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
You don't know Haruto?
It hurts.
Let me hold it.
I'm sorry.
Do you like Haruto?
I don't know.
Say it with your ears.
You don't know?
I don't know.
Let's do it together.
Do you know Haruto?
I don't know.
It hurts.
I love you.
I love you too.
I love you Haruto.
I want to forget Haruto.
I'll let you forget him.
Is it still here?
I don't know.
It hurts.
Yuzu.
I don't know.
acrylic paint is not strong enough, right?
Because
Haruto is the same as me.
I don't know.
Stop it.
Yuzu.
I don't know.
Haruto,
stop it.
I don't know.
Stop it.
Yuzu,
I feel good.
Yuzu's belly is soft.
I love you.
Yuzu.
I feel good.
Yuzu,
I love you.
Yuzu is kind.
I couldn't let go of Haruto.
Haruto always
admit that I have to clean hisiments together with you.
It's so pitiful,
I just cleaned his air bubbles with a plastic towel.
Yuzu won't tell him well,
That's true.
Haruna is here,
I just want you to open the door.
I like Haruna more than Haruto.
Then I won't tell Haruto.
You're just so pitiful.
I can make Yuzu more happy.
Me?
Yuzu is so pitiful.
I feel so bad.
Yuzu is so pitiful,
I know a lot about him.
He's gone.
Haruto doesn't know anything, does he?
I feel so bad.
You like being forced to do this.
Haruto.
No.
Yuzu.
Go, go.
I like you.
I like Yuzu too.
It's so pitiful.
Did you write something?
No one is here.
Please cry more.
No.
Please cry about me too.
Please cry more.
I feel so bad too.
I feel so bad.
Yuzu.
It's so warm.
I feel so bad.
Yuzu, you're so pitiful.
Yuzu.
I like you.
I like you too.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
I feel so bad.
Yuzu, your belly is so hot.
Yuzu.
Are you crying?
I'm sorry.
I feel so bad.
I feel too bad.
Why do I feel so bad?
She won't be the first to come.
When I was bullied,
when I was in university,
when I was sick,
she was always by my side.
When I was in a pitiful spring,
but
I love that face of despair.
What?
I don't know what to say.
What's so fun about taking away my precious things?
I'm not taking them away.
I'm always
just thinking about something.
I'm not taking them away.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
I knew it.
I feel so bad.
Stop it.
What's this?
You like it, don't you?
You're a pervert.
Look.
It's in your mouth.
It's dirty.
How does it feel?
It's amazing.
What's this?
It's like a baby.
It's dirty.
What do you feel now?
Where are you going?
Why did you go through the door?
Look here.
What's this?
You're moving more and more.
It's dirty.
You said you were strong.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
It's dirty.
Don't cry.
What's this?
It's dirty.
Did you say it again?
It's strange.
Do you know what this is?
I don't know.
It's like a girl.
It's called an eye breath.
You can't do this.
I can't do this anymore.
It's amazing.
Look here.
It's strange.
I can't do this anymore.
You said it again.
It's strange.
Is it strange?
Do you want to take a bath?
You're listening, aren't you?
Answer me properly.
That's...
I want to take a bath.
I can do this.
It's strange.
What?
I want to take a bath.
It hurts.
Close your legs.
It's different when you hit it, isn't it?
It's strange.
It hurts.
It's different when you hit it, isn't it?
You're not breathing.
I'm tired.
It hurts.
You're not breathing.
I'm tired.
What?
Is this okay?
It hurts.
I wanted you to do this.
It's not.
I want to see it.
It hurts.
It's gone.
Here?
It hurts.
I won't let you do this.
I want you to do this.
I want to see it.
I want you to let me do this.
Please let me do this.
I can't hear you.
You're Luna, right?
Please let me do this.
It's okay.
It hurts.
Luna, come here.
What's wrong?
Luna, it hurts.
That's it!
I want to do this.
It hurts.
That face.
That pathetic face.
Do you love it?
Luna.
You don't have time to rest.
Let me touch you.
It hurts so much.
That's it.
What do you think?
It hurts.
You don't have time to rest.
What should I do?
Please.
It hurts so much.
I can't even breathe.
Should I go?
No.
I don't want to.
Wait a minute.
It hurts so much.
Yuzu.
You heard it from my room.
What?
No way.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to sleep.
You're in a hurry.
You said Yuzu was next to you.
You're a pervert.
No.
I can love you.
I'm okay.
I don't want to.
Why don't you sleep?
It hurts so much.
You don't have to.
Is this for me?
I want to sleep.
I'm in a hurry.
Do you want me to walk you?
Yes.
I can walk you.
Here.
Put your hands on me.
Don't come near me.
Don't touch me.
Don't stop me.
I'm so sorry.
Don't touch me.
You still want to do it, don't you?
Don't you want to do it?
Don't touch me.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm really going to sleep.
Don't touch me.
I'm going to sleep.
Look at the wall around you.
You can enjoy it.
Don't touch me.
I told you.
I always...
I always do what you want me to do.
Don't touch me.
You're the best.
Haruto.
You don't deserve to be a man.
Am I right?
Yes.
What do you want?
I want a dog.
I see.
Haruto.
What are you doing?
This is wrong.
What do you mean?
It's weird, Haruto.
Don't take it off.
Haruto was like that.
You're a human, aren't you?
You're a dog, aren't you?
Yes.
Haruto.
Say it to Haruto.
I'm a dog.
Hurry up.
You're wrong.
You're a dog, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm a dog.
What do you want, Haruto?
I don't want to see you.
I don't want you to see me more.
Haruto, I'm taking it off.
Hurry up and walk.
Sit down.
You're going to give up, aren't you?
Yes.
Don't be shy.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm looking at you.
I didn't think you'd do that, Haruto.
I'm sorry.
Good looking.
What?
What's wrong?
I want to take it off.
No?
Yes.
Take it off.
You want to take it off, don't you?
Yes.
Sit down.
Wait.
Haruto.
Can I look at you?
I want to take it off.
You really want to be a dog?
Yes.
I want to take it off.
I want to be a dog.
Haruto.
You don't want to be a dog?
Yes.
Oh my god.
Who is it?
Take it off.
It's not good at all.
Damn it.
Take it off.
Look over there.
Do you have a lead?
Yes.
Yuzu.
The lead of a dog is to put your thumb here and hold it like this.
Hold it like this.
Good.
Look.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
Do you feel like you're sleeping?
Haruto.
It's really weird.
Yes.
What's your cry?
Haruto.
What are you looking forward to?
I'm feeling it.
I thought you would kiss me.
Hey, Haruto.
It's not like that.
Kiss you.
Hey.
Look over here.
It's not good at all.
Yes.
Hey.
Sleep.
Yes.
Show me the lead.
The lead.
What are you talking about?
Haruto.
Yes.
Show me the lead.
More.
Yes.
I feel bad, Haruto.
You feel bad, don't you?
Why are you so excited?
I can't help it.
It's weird to be like this.
It's weird.
I feel it even if I get bitten.
I'm sorry.
I feel bad.
What are you feeling?
I'm sorry.
A dog's steal.
Yes.
Look at this.
A dog.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
What are you trying to steal?
A pervert.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
A dog?
I'm sorry.
A dog is a dog.
My favorite Yuzu.
She is looking at me with a shy face.
Do you have a smoke?
I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
Are you okay?
Yuzu is looking at you.
I'm sorry.
Yuzu is looking at you
Yuzu is looking at me
I'm sorry.
Yuzu looking at you.
Are you okay?
Kiss me?
What are you doing?
I told you I like you
This guy is like this
I like you
I'm sorry
Yuzu
You're the worst
I'm sorry
You're making me angry
You're not a child
I'm sorry
Yuzu
Shut up
Show me how you feel
Then Yuzu might come back
I'm sorry
You can't do it
Yuzu
You couldn't do it
Come here
I'm so embarrassed
Are you embarrassed?
I'm embarrassed
You're so embarrassed
I'm sorry
That's not good
Come here
Wait
You don't have to let me go, do you?
I'm embarrassed
Please let me go
I'm a dog
You can wait
I'm embarrassed
You don't have to let me go
Wait, don't take it
Don't take it
But
I'm embarrassed
Wait
Wait, don't take it
I'm embarrassed
Don't take it
Wait
Please let me go
I'm embarrassed
You're a dog
You're not saying anything
I'm sorry
You're wrong
You're a dog
I'm so close
What?
Don't call me
I'm sorry
What are you doing?
I'm embarrassed
So
You're saying it
I'm embarrassed
Don't look at me
I don't like it
It's the same as always
Look
This embarrassing school
It's okay
I'm embarrassed
If you keep going like this
Your face will be covered
I'm embarrassed
Please let me go
Are you going to be a telephoto?
No
Please let me go
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm embarrassed
Hold on
Yes
Come on, Haruto
What?
I love you, Haruto
Your food
Bring it to me
It's so ticklish
Are you happy?
Yes
Oh, no
Haruto
What are you doing here?
This is
a towel
Really?
First, this
Yuzu
Look closely
I'm taking a video
Oh, no
It's so ticklish
Really?
Oh, no
It's so ticklish
Here?
This is a towel
It's so ticklish
Is it okay?
But
Here?
This is a towel
Look
It's a towel
Yuzu
Japan
No, no
It's so ticklish
No
Look closely
Haruto, you want me to look at you, right?
No
Oh, no
What's in there?
It's gone
Oh, there
Here?
It's in
Oh, no
Yuzu
Yuzu, look closely
Look
The two of you
How, Haruto?
It's so ticklish
It's a pervert
Here?
Look
Look at this messy face
It's really Yuzu
Yuzu
It's so ticklish
It's a pervert
It's really Yuzu
Yuzu
It's not there, right?
Oh
It's getting in
You know what it looks like
I know
It's in the back
Haruto
It's so ticklish
Yuzu
It's not there
There?
It's over there
No
It could be
over there
It wasn't there
You want me to hold your hand?
Oh
It's going
It's over there
I'm going to cry
Show me where to breathe
I'm sorry
What are you doing?
It's a dog
It's not there
I'm sorry
I can't stop it
It's hard
It's so hard
It feels good
I can't stop it
It's bad
It feels bad
It feels good
Look
Look at Yuzu's face
What should I do?
My butt
Don't say it
Look
It's going
Did you say it?
It feels bad
It's going
What should I do?
On your face
It's going
What's wrong?
Your surprised face
It's going
It's just a deal
Yuzu
It's good
It's going
I say it
It feels good
It's going
Okay
I don't know
It's going
You just need to be quiet and stand up
It's the same
It really is
I can do it if I'm in front of you
Yes
That face
It's going
Sometimes, it can be useful
Look
I helped you
Yuzu
You helped me
I'm glad
Yuzu helped me
You said you liked me so much
I'm going to give you a kiss
Yuzu
I love you
When I do this
Yuzu gets more and more
I feel like I'm in Yuzu
Yuzu
It feels good
Don't talk to me
I'm sorry
I feel like I'm in Yuzu's heart
Please feel it
Yuzu
I love you
What's wrong?
Are you looking at me?
Yes
Yuzu
Are you looking at me?
I feel good
Why did you talk to me?
It was a good thing
I'm not going to talk to you
I'm sorry
You said you were going to leave
That's right
Show me your face
I'm sorry
Yuzu, are you mad at me?
No way
I hate you
Don't get in my way
Don't say that
I love you
Shut up
I don't need you anymore
Hey, Yuzu
You're cute
I love you
I love you more
I told you I love you
I told you I don't love you
I don't need you anymore
This is real news
I found it
You said something weird
Don't do that
I feel bad
Give it back
Yuzu
Don't do that
Please
I told you to stop
I'll take it for you
I can't take it
Don't do that
I'm sorry
I don't understand
I'm sorry Yuzu
I'm sorry
Wait
What?
Did you put it inside?
I put it inside
I put something inside
I'm sorry
Are you okay?
I'm okay
I want to give it back
I'll give it back soon
I'm not satisfied
Wait
Why?
Put it inside
Wait
Why did you put it inside?
This face
I don't know
Yuzu