It's so delicious that I can't stop thinking about it.
Let's make it simple.
Cheers.
It's sweet.
It's delicious.
I think so.
It's really good.
Really?
It's a letter from my father.
I see.
It's really good.
It's a letter from my father.
It's not like that.
I'm not sure.
It's okay.
I'm glad you're happy.
I was really looking forward to it.
Really?
I've always said that Michiru is
really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
I haven't had a boyfriend in 6 years.
I think it's because you're so pretty.
I'm not sure.
To be honest,
I really like the one that Echibu likes.
It's cute.
I think it's true.
I'm not sure.
I'm so embarrassed.
I think it's because you like it.
This is the one that Echibu likes.
The one that Echibu likes.
That's not the case.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm going to take a picture.
What's coming out?
Well...
This one.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed.
I usually don't like this one.
I'm going to take a picture.
I'll show you.
Ah, it's nice.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I'm embarrassed.
It's nice.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm not going to get married again.
I'm going to get married again.
I want to get married.
I'm a friend.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat this.
It's delicious.
How is it?
I have to hurry up.
I'm not going to get married again.
I think you can make it right away.
I don't have a boyfriend.
Everyone has a girlfriend.
What?
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat this.
It's cute.
I'm not going to get married.
I'm going to get married with a friend.
I'm not going to get married with a friend.
Let's go
I have to eat vegetables.
I hate broccoli.
I always think that broccoli is bad.
I was happy that it was his wish.
broccoli is bad, too.
broccoli is very good.
I hate broccoli.
It's good.
broccoli is cute.
Is it?
He said it was cute.
Stop saying that I'm a good guy.
I'm so jealous.
I'll eat more.
It's delicious.
I'm a good guy.
I'm a bad guy.
I drank alcohol.
Did you drink alcohol?
I'm a bad guy.
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
You're in a hurry.
I'm in a hurry.
I'm told.
Are you okay?
Do you drink water?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Do you want me to bring you something?
If I didn't drink alcohol, I would have drank it.
Now?
I'm in a hurry.
What do you do with the gel?
Can you teach me how to use the gel?
No.
It's a smear.
How do you use the gel?
What do you do with it?
I can't hear you.
It's not a problem.
I'm in a hurry.
You're really in a hurry.
I can't hear you.
I'm in a hurry.
My hair is not straight.
It's not straight.
I'm in a hurry.
My hair is not straight.
Bye.
Are you saying that I'm trying to get on your wife?
Yes?
I'm trying to make sure she is safe.
I'm.
I just said something to wake you up.
I say water.
Sorry.
I'm sorry at all.
You're okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I was late.
Thank you.
Are you hungry?
I'm really hungry.
Thank you.
Are you eating?
Yes, I'm eating.
It's really delicious.
It's really good curry.
You're really good at eating curry.
I'm really good at eating curry.
I want to eat salmon.
Is there something?
I have ice cream.
Is it okay to eat because there is ice cream?
It's okay to eat because there is ice cream.
I have ice cream.
Thank you.
It's really good curry.
I like that kind of curry.
That's right.
I want to be in front of you.
It's light, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I want to drink it.
Do you want to drink a lot?
Yes.
Do you want to take a break?
Do you want me to eat it?
Was it delicious?
Yes, it was delicious.
It's delicious.
It was delicious only after a while.
It was delicious, wasn't it?
Yes.
I will make it for you.
Thank you.
Do you want to eat it?
What?
I ate it.
What should I do?
What?
I want to eat it.
Thank you.
Are you sleeping?
You are sleeping.
Let me clean it.
Mr. Honoka.
I was sleeping.
Don't worry.
I'm not sleeping.
It's painful.
What?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I was surprised.
What?
Are you having a hard time?
It's painful.
I'm not having a hard time.
Did you have a hard time?
I was surprised.
Mr. Honoka, are you sleeping again?
Yes.
I'm not sleeping.
Mr. Honoka.
Hello.
Are you having a hard time?
Yes.
I'm not having a hard time.
Please don't eat it.
I'm not feeling it.
I'm getting bigger.
Are you okay?
I can't see you because you're sleeping.
I'm not feeling very well, so I'm going to drink some water.
Is it okay?
I'm not feeling very well.
Are you having a hard time?
Yes.
Why don't you take a bath with me?
I'm not feeling well.
Okay.
I see.
Do you like big boobs?
What?
What do you mean?
Do you like them or don't you like them?
I don't like them.
I see.
Look.
I'm not feeling well.
I see.
Please calm down.
My boobs are big.
I see.
Ouch!
Are you crying?
Are you two felling pain?
I see.
Are you having a hard time?
Please stop.
It's painful.
It's really painful.
But...
It's painful.
I can't stand it anymore.
What should I do?
It's really painful.
It's painful.
What?
Actually, I like to be looked at.
You're wrong.
That's not true.
Then, why do you feel like this?
Let me see.
It's not good.
What?
I see.
You're touching your forehead.
I'm touching it.
You were touching it.
You don't have to lie.
I'll show you my greed.
It's really not good.
Then...
Ouch!
It's painful.
Why are you getting so big?
No.
It's painful.
There's a lot of pain here.
I can feel it.
Wait a minute.
It's painful.
It's dirty.
I don't feel like I'm being looked at.
It's painful.
If you don't like it, don't resist it.
No.
Please don't do that.
Wait a minute.
It's painful.
Please don't do that.
It's okay.
If you don't like it, don't do that.
No.
It's painful.
You're getting so big.
No.
It's painful.
Wait a minute.
What should I do?
It's painful.
Wait a minute.
Please don't do that.
It's painful.
I don't like it when you're coming up to me like this.
It's really strange.
It's painful.
Come here.
I want to do something that I can't do on the road.
If I don't have a lot of hair, I can't do it.
It's painful.
I hid my hair in a bag like this.
I'm going to get caught.
Let's stop.
Are you going to stop?
Can I really stop here?
It's painful.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
Let's do something more comfortable.
Are you okay?
It's painful.
It's getting thicker.
Steven.
It's painful.
It's not good.
It's not good?
It's not good, right?
Do it again.
Like this?
No.
Please eat it.
It's not good.
It's painful.
I can't do it.
It's not easy to walk.
How are you always?
It's not like this.
It's painful.
Do you feel better than usual?
No.
I don't want to say it.
Why?
Do you want to do it more?
No.
You can't say it, right?
Please eat it.
It's painful.
You can't say it, right?
It's not good.
Come here.
You can't say it, right?
It's painful.
Please eat it.
Please eat this.
It's painful.
Thank you.
Please eat this.
It's painful.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I had a lot of trouble.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh, my God.
You're getting bigger now.
Do you want to do it again?
No, I don't want to do it again.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to do it again.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
I did it again.
Do you want to do it again?
No, I don't want to do it again.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it again?
You want me to do it again, right?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
Why are you sleeping here?
You're getting up soon.
What?
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Hey, did you have fun?
You must be sleepy.
Oh, I see.
Hey, mother.
Stop getting a fan on your friends.
Oh, I see.
What are you doing on the way?
I see.
Do you go home in the morning?
Oh, I see.
Nui, be careful.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sad.
I see.
Did you forget?
Oh, my God.
I see.
Did you think you were going home?
Oh, my God.
Did you want to go home?
Oh, I see.
You don't come home until the morning, do you?
Oh, my God.
How do you see?
Oh?
Oh, my God.
I see.
You didn't come home, did you?
No, I didn't.
Oh, my God.
What?
You don't get sick, do you?
No.
I am.
You don't get sick, do you?
Here.
Oh, my God.
Oh?
You can't do that.
Here.
I can't believe you're here.
What?
You can't go back to the house.
I can't believe you're here.
Please don't cry.
Why?
Why can't I drink it?
I can't drink it.
What?
I can't hear you.
Oh, my God.
I feel so much better.
Bye.
Oh, my God.
You can't do that.
You thought you were going to get sick, didn't you?
Come on.
Go back.
What do you think?
You're going to be treated like this.
Have you ever been treated like this?
No.
Can you teach me how to treat you?
What do you mean?
Oh, my God.
What are you going to do?
Show me.
I can't see my butt.
Oh, my God.
You can't do that.
Don't put it down.
Oh, my God.
I can feel your butt.
Show me your butt.
Oh, my God.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't see my butt.
Oh, my God.
I can't see well.
I can't.
I can't see.
I just hit.
Wait a minute.
No.
What are you going to do?
This is my first time.
If you feel better,
I want you to do something more comfortable.
Go away.
It's my first time.
Don't hurry.
It's amazing.
It's painful.
Are you okay?
It's my first time.
I can't do it tomorrow.
Are you okay?
Don't cry.
It's painful.
I don't know how many times I said it.
I'm so nervous.
I said it was okay to say it.
It's painful.
Are you crying?
It's painful because I've only worked for you.
It's painful, isn't it?
Do you want to make me feel better?
Do you want me to do it?
It's painful.
Put it inside your body.
And?
It's painful.
Which one do you want to drink?
I can't decide.
You can't decide?
Then I'll stop.
No, goodbye.
Which one?
I feel much better.
I feel much better now.
It's really painful.
It's painful.
I feel much better now.
What's wrong?
It's painful.
I feel so painful.
Where are you going?
I'm going to there.
It's painful.
It hurts.
That hurts.
It's painful.
It hurts.
Next time, I'll take a deep breath.
It hurts so much.
Wait a sec.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
Mother is crying.
She's crying so much.
It hurts.
Mother is crying so much.
Do you know that she's crying?
It hurts so much.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm feeling so much better.
Are you okay?
Mother is crying so much again.
It hurts so much.
Mother is crying so much.
Are you okay?
I'm feeling so much better.
It hurts so much.
Please calm down.
Why are you crying so much?
I'm going to cry if I don't do that.
Are you okay?
I'm feeling so much better.
Mother is crying so much.
Do you understand?
I'm feeling so much better.
It hurts so much.
Itch.
It's not over yet.
I can't do it anymore.
Itch.
It's not over yet.
I'm feeling so much better.
Are you alright?
I drank too much water.
I'm feeling so much better.
I wasn't expecting this.
What?
Is it because you're in my room?
Please, hold this.
I'm feeling so much better.
What's wrong?
I've never done such a intense sex.
I'm tired.
You're feeling better, aren't you?
You can't see this, can you?
What?
Are you feeling better?
I'm feeling so much better.
Do you want to eat the tea made by Michiru?
Really?
Yes.
Let's eat together.
Here you go.
It looks delicious.
Do you want to eat it?
Yes.
Thank you for the food.
You're so good at cooking.
You're right.
I'm hungry.
Do you want to eat it?
No, it's not that.
You can only hear it like that.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's good.
Michiru is a good cook.
Yes, she is.
Which sex do you prefer, Michiru or me?
I don't know.
Which sex?
I'm sorry, Michiru.
I don't know the answer.
I'm alone, so it's okay.
It's okay.
Next.
Here you go.
I don't like broccoli.
You don't like it?
Yes.
You can't eat it?
No, I can't eat it.
You want me to eat it?
If you can't eat it, I'll eat it.
Is it good?
Yes.
Why do you eat broccoli if it's me?
It's good.
Yes, it's good.
Do you like me?
No, it's not like that.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
No, it's close.
Is it too close?
No.
I'll eat it now.
You seem to be happy again.
Yes.
You are the most honest person.
Michiru.
What's wrong?
It's not good.
What?
You said it's not good.
You touched my butt.
I didn't touch it.
You didn't touch it.
Your mouth is different from mine.
It's strange here.
I'll make you feel better.
What's that?
Look.
Look over here.
Look here.
It's strange here.
Have you ever done something like this?
No.
It's a new feeling, isn't it?
It's strange here.
You really like it.
It's good.
It's strange here.
I'll make you feel better.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Do you want me to feel better?
It's strange here.
Look.
Are you feeling better?
It's strange here.
You said you don't like it.
But now you feel better.
It's strange here.
Oh my.
Wow!
It's quietゲーム.
It's so cute!
Oh no.
You'd better not wake up.
No.
I want to go.
You want to go?
You said you'd go to the end of the road.
You said you'd go bad if you did this.
I want to go.
I want to do something more comfortable.
Something more comfortable?
Yes.
Do you know the word MESUIKI?
MESUIKI?
What's that?
Ta-da!
Do you want me to teach you?
What's that?
It's like a girl.
You can do it many times.
What do you mean?
You shouldn't look at me.
What are you doing?
I don't know what you're doing.
It's a butt.
It's not there.
What are you doing?
It's a butt.
And then...
You do this.
You're going to be in the front and back.
You're going to be in the back.
What's that?
It's a butt.
I've never had a butt.
I'm going to make you feel good.
You came here early.
It's so funny.
I've never seen you do that.
It's fun.
It hurts.
It's moving.
I hit it with my butt.
I don't know.
Why is it moving?
It's moving.
It's so painful.
It's not over yet.
It's getting more and more painful.
It's a mess.
It's moving again.
It hurts.
It's moving.
It's moving again.
It's the first time that it's moving.
It looks like it's going to be a habit.
It's moving again.
It's okay.
I want to be good at it.
It's moving again.
I took a picture with my butt hole.
Look.
There are a lot of warriors.
Do you know what this is?
What is it?
It's called Tokorote.
Tokorote.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
But it's not over yet.
What?
It's not over yet.
Wake up.
I see.
It's a lot.
It makes me feel better.
I'll make you feel better with your butt hole.
It's moving again.
It's not over yet.
It was supposed to be over.
It's moving again.
It's not over yet.
It was supposed to be over.
It's moving again.
It's not over yet.
Are you okay?
Did you feel a lot of pain?
Yes.
I feel so dizzy.
Are you okay?
Do you want to try again?
Look.
Are you okay?
I feel so dizzy.
Wow.
Why did you put out the Holy Spirit again?
I feel so dizzy.
Do you want me to tell you something more?
I'm still dizzy.
I'm glad that you did what you did.
Holy Spirit?
I didn't notice you.
You were there all the time?
Yes.
I was waiting for you to come.
I was surprised that you were here.
Are you okay?
I feel so dizzy.
I'm glad that you did what you did.
I want you to tell me something more.
Something more?
Wait a minute.
I feel dizzy.
What are you going to do?
I'm looking forward to it.
Are you okay with this?
No.
I'm glad that you did what you did.
What is this?
I wonder what it is.
I feel dizzy.
Is it too strong?
It feels good, isn't it?
Where are you going?
I can't see you.
What do you want to do with me?
It's okay.
I want you to feel good.
I want you to touch my hips.
It's not good.
It's not good at all.
It's okay.
I feel dizzy.
It's not good at all.
Are you going?
Yes, hurry up!
I want to go tomorrow.
Do you want to go more today?
Do you want to go better tomorrow?
I feel better because I'm going to go yesterday.
Let's go this way.
No, no, no.
You can say no when you say no, right?
Do you want to see?
Yes, I want to see.
No, no, no.
Come here.
Show me.
It's embarrassing.
No, it's embarrassing.
I can see your butt.
Don't touch me.
But I'm looking for you.
I'm looking for you.
No, you can't.
The baby is in.
It's in.
No, you can't.
Look at this.
What is it?
It's not in.
You have to try it.
No, you can't.
It's not in.
It's in.
You can put it in slowly.
My butt is shaking.
How does it feel?
It's in.
Let's go.
No, you can't.
You can't?
My butt is in.
It's in.
It's like a water.
How many are in it?
It's in.
I'm sorry, mom.
It's in?
It's in.
Something like can feel it.
It is.
It's in.
It's in a smile.
It's okay.
It's in?
It's in.
It's in in.
I'm on it.
It's in.
No, no, no.
You put it out twice.
You remembered something new.
Can you sleep with this?
Let's sleep together.
What are you doing?
Are you awake?
Why?
Did you get tired of sleeping yesterday?
Yes.
So,
I'll make you feel sexy next time.
Sexy?
I'm not awake.
I'm not awake at all.
I'm not tired.
I'm not awake.
Let's eat.
You can make this kind of food.
It's good.
I can't eat.
I want to eat more than rice.
Wait a minute.
It's here.
It's too sudden.
Wait a minute.
I want to make you feel more comfortable than you do.
Me too?
I want you to feel the most comfortable.
You want me to do it, don't you?
How do you feel?
I want you to do it.
From behind.
It's scary.
It's too sudden.
Let's put this on together.
What is this?
It's too sudden.
Let's put this on together.
What is this?
It's too sudden.
Let's put this on together.
What is this?
It's too sudden.
Wait a minute.
Well, I've been watching TV all the time.
I've been cleaning.
It's too sudden.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, I forgot to put on my clothes.
Honoka-chan, what are you doing?
I didn't touch you.
You didn't touch me, did you?
It's too sudden.
I don't think I'm good at this.
I'll make you an unforgettable body.
It's too sudden.
It hurts.
Honoka-chan, what are you doing?
Honoka-chan, come here.
It hurts.
Honoka-chan, you are very sensitive.
What should I do?
Do you want to be more sensitive?
I want to be more sensitive.
Then, I will make you feel more sensitive.
You can do it.
It hurts.
Honoka-chan, you are very sensitive.
Next, I will make you feel better.
It hurts.
Thank you for watching.